what's up everybody all
やぁ、みんな
I'm Taichi Kamakazy I got a new nick name and I got new tatoo, Kamakazy
太一"カマカジ"です、どーも。新しいニックネーム、タトゥを手に入れたぜ、カミカゼだ。
ok,today
今日は
I'm visiting Tokyo
東京に来ているところだ。
for talking with KTM Japan
KTMジャパンと打ち合わせをして
RedBull Japan...
レッドブルジャパンとも打ち合わせをした。
I share about erzberg.
エルズベルグのことをシェアしてきたよ。
talking a long time.
長い時間をかけてね。
This year for me last challenge for erzbergrodeo
今年はオレにとって、エルズベルグロデオは最後のチャレンジになる
I mean, because...
つまり...
Five year is
5年間
so many time I try
何度もトライしてきた。
always I talking with Redbull and KTM
いつもレッドブルとKTMと話してきた
about Offroad scene in Japan
日本でのオフロードシーンは
situation is not so good now.
あまり状況がよくないことを。
But I wanna change.This is wanna wanna do exactly.
オレは、それを変えたいんだ。やりたいのはそういうこと。
important things I have to get podium.
そのためにも、ポディウムが必要だ。
3rd position.
最低でも3位。
My target
それが目標。
But anyway you know in the streets
ストリートでも
we have very good idea
オレたちはいいアイデアを持ってる。
It's public viewing
パブリックビューイングだね。
In city,everybody group
街中で、みんなが
Redbull
レッドブルの
website
ウェブサイトを見れるようにね。
Maybe, I need good start
たぶん、いいスタートが切れれば
I don't mistake prologue,
プロローグ（予選）でミスしなければ
it's very risky and fast
それはすごくリスキーで、速度の乗るあぶない予選なんだけど
training a lot,now but still working normal job
トレーニングはちゃんとしてる。普段の仕事もしながらね。
Japanese Offroad rider is
日本のオフロードライダーは
very tough
とってもタフだぜ。
I ride this "war".
オレはこの「戦争」に乗るんだ
I don't care. I'm tough
心配いらない、オレはタフだから。
I can show you Japanese people
オレは証明できる。日本人が
how much strong
どれだけ強いかを。
very strong.
とても強いんだ。
Many year ago like KAMIKAZE we lose the war
遠い昔、我々は戦争に負けた。
America
アメリカに。
we just a game
ただのゲームなんだ。
we play the game offroad racing,you know?
オレたちは、オフロードレースをゲームとしてやってる。そうだろ？
So
だから
You are very rich man.because no war nobody fight.
戦争もなく、豊かに暮らしてる
motorcycle game
モーターサイクルのゲームだ。
I don't wanna lose
負けたくは無い。
any country
どんな国にも。
and we have a
オレたちには
many young kids Japanese right.
若いキッズ達がたくさんいる。
I wanna kids
キッズ達には
I don't wanna say it's like a dream.
言って欲しくない。夢のようだなんて。
I wanna be rich man I wanna be star
オレはリッチになりたいし、スターになりたい
is same thinking
同じ事を考えてる。
Child too
子供達も。
So
だから
I try Erzberg
オレはエルズベルグにトライする
explain local people
ローカルの人間達に説明するときは
I wanna make a more measured
もっとメジャーしたいんだって言う。
I wanna win erzberg
エルズベルグで勝ちたい。
for Everybody more excite. This is wanna wanna do.
みんなを興奮させるためにね。それがしたいことだ。
KTM Japan boss
KTMジャパンのボスや
and guys of Redbull Japan
レッドブルジャパンのクルー達に
give me a lot of the help
たくさん助けられている。
This year, Taichi Kamakazy don't forget
今年は、カミカゼタイチを忘れるな。
very very strong!
最高に強いぜ。
And I have new idea
それと、新しいアイデアがあるんだ。
after the finish erzberg
エルズベルグが終わったら
I wanna organaze endurocross Japan
日本でエンデューロクロスをオーガナイズしたい。
And I wanna ride ISDE.
それとISDEに出たいね。
Best six rider of Japanese
日本のベストの6人だ。
I wanna make new team.
オレは新しいチームを作りたい。
Best riders in Japan.
ベストのライダーでね。
I can show you
見せられるはずだ。
we can show you,How much strong Japanese rider is
日本のライダーが
how much strong. We have very strong mentarity
どれだけ強いかを。オレたちの精神力は強い。
We have many problems but
多くの問題はあるけど
We never forget never give up.
忘れないし、絶対にギブアップしない。
After erzberg
エルズベルグのあとには
We see Japanese endurocross.
日本のエンデューロクロスだ。
This is wanna. what I thinking.
これが、今、オレが考えてること。
OK,Thanks
聞いてくれてありがとう
Sayonara.See you in Erzberg!
バイバイ、それじゃエルズベルグで会おう！